## **Wesley Agena**

(808) 226-3962 1123 N92nd St. Apt. 2, Seattle, WA 98103 wesley.agena@gmail.com wesleyagena.com

# Professional Profile

My career includes a strong focus on Back End web development as a PHP developer for the past 5 years.

I also enjoy working with Front End and DevOps through side projects, where I experiment with current frameworks, design patterns, and modern technologies.

**Expert** - production experience 5+ years, serving 600+ million PHP requests/day.

PHP, MySQL, Git, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS,

Familiar - used in side projects, or on a semi-regular basis for 5+ years.

- Laravel, Rest APIs, PHPUnit, Selenium, JQuery, Javascript, VueJS, ES6, LESS
- Gulp, Vagrant (Homestead), Linux, NGINX, Apache

#### **Work History**

#### **April 2014 - February 2016**

Senior Software Developer, Accretive Technology Group

- Port legacy payable library to REST API used across multiple products.
- Built user + internal facing system for submission, review, storage of documents (Drivers License, Passports, etc).

#### October 2011 - April 2014

Software Developer, Accretive Technology Group

 Tool allowing users to query clients based on certain spending habits, and build inmail campaigns targeting those clients.

### **Education**

Masters in Engineering Science - Computer Science University of the Pacific - Stockton, CA

Graduate Assistantship in Computer Science

June 2010 - September 2011

BS Computer Science - Networking and Security

University of the Pacific - Stockton, CA

Academic Excellence Award for Computer Science, Presidents Scholarship, UOP Grant, FIT

May 2005 - May 2010